John V. Dowdy, Sr. papers, Inclusive: 1926-1986, undated; Bulk: 1952-1972, undated.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Personal, 1930-1986, undated; 7
  - Political, circa 1940--1972, undated; 6
    - Campaign Materials, General, 1965 (Box 466, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Materials, Song, 1966 (Box 466, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Materials, General (1 of 4), 1966 (Box 466, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Materials, General (2 of 4), 1966 (Box 466, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Materials, General (3 of 4), 1966 (Box 466, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Materials, General (4 of 4), 1966 (Box 466, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Anderson, 1966 (Box 466, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Angelina (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 467, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Angelina (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 467, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Hardin, 1966 (Box 467, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Henderson, 1966 (Box 467, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Houston, 1966 (Box 467, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Jasper, 1966 (Box 467, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Liberty, 1966 (Box 467, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Montgomery, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Nacogdoches, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Newton, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Orange, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Polk, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Sabine, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-San Augustine, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-San Jacinto, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Trinity, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Tyler, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Walker, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Materials, Dies, Martin Jr., 1966 (Box 469, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Materials, Election Certificate, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Materials, International Neighbors Club, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-General, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Anderson County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Angelina County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Hardin County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Henderson County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Houston County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Jasper County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Liberty County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Montgomery County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 12)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Nacogdoches County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 13)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Newton County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 14)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Orange County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 15)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Polk County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 16)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Sabine County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 17)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-San Augustine County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 18)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Trinity County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 19)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Tyler County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 20)
    - Campaign Materials, List of Supporters-Walker County, 1966 (Box 469, Folder 21)
    - Campaign Materials, Out of District: A-K (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 469, Folder 22)
    - Campaign Materials, Out of District: A-K (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 469, Folder 23)
    - Campaign Materials, Out of District: L-Z, 1966 (Box 470, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Materials, Supporters (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 470, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Materials, Supporters (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 470, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Materials, General, 1968 (Box 470, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Materials, News Clippings, 1968 (Box 470, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Anderson, 1968 (Box 470, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Angelina, 1968 (Box 470, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Hardin, 1968 (Box 470, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Henderson, 1968 (Box 470, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Houston, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Jasper, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Liberty, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Montgomery, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Nacogdoches, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Newton, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Orange, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Polk, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Sabine, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-San Augustine, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-San Jacinto, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Trinity, 1968 (Box 471, Folder 12)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Tyler, 1968 (Box 472, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Walker, 1968 (Box 472, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Materials, Media, 1968 (Box 472, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Materials, Out of District: A-D, 1968 (Box 472, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Materials, Out of District: E-O, 1968 (Box 472, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Materials, Out of District: P-Z, 1968 (Box 472, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Materials, Vote Total, 1968 (Box 472, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Materials, General, 1969 (Box 472, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Materials, General, 1970 (Box 472, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Angelina, 1970 (Box 472, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Anderson, 1970 (Box 472, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Hardin, 1970 (Box 472, Folder 12)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Henderson, 1970 (Box 473, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Houston, 1970 (Box 473, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Jasper, 1970 (Box 473, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Montgomery, 1970 (Box 473, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Orange, 1970 (Box 473, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Trinity, 1970 (Box 473, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Materials, Counties-Tyler, 1970 (Box 473, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Materials, Out-of-District, 1970 (Box 473, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Materials, General, 1971 (Box 473, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Materials, General (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 473, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Materials, General (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 473, Folder 11)
  - Publications, 1937-1974, undated; 7
    - “A Voice in the Wilderness”, 1973-1974 (Box 473, Folder 12)
    - The Advanced Economics Society, 1937 (Box 473, Folder 13)
    - “The American Adviser” No. 48, 1974 March 12 (Box 473, Folder 14)
    - Americans for Constitutional Action, 1960-1971 (Box 473, Folder 15)
    - Anti-Communism, 1944-1957 (Box 473, Folder 16)
    - Anti-Communism, 1960-1969 (Box 473, Folder 17)
    - Anti-Communism, 1970-1975, undated (Box 473, Folder 18)
    - “The Astronauts Did Not Walk on the Moon”, 1972 (Box 473, Folder 19)
    - “Is Small Business Doomed?”, 1953 (Box 473, Folder 20)
    - Campus Radicals, 1970 (Box 473, Folder 21)
    - Common Sense, 1958-1965 (Box 473, Folder 22)
    - Committee to Restore the Constitution, Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 473, Folder 23)
    - Confederate Government of America, 1961 (Box 473, Folder 24)
    - Conservatives, Ultra, 1963-1970 (Box 473, Folder 25)
    - Constitution Party, 1952, 1960 (Box 474, Folder 1)
    - The Cross and the Flag, 1959, 1965-1966 (Box 474, Folder 2)
    - “Dan Smoot Report”, 1953-1967 (Box 474, Folder 3)
    - Defenders of the American Constitution, Inc., 1954, 1974 (Box 474, Folder 4)
    - Defense, 1954 (Box 474, Folder 5)
    - Die Brüde, 1974 (Box 474, Folder 6)
    - “Don Bell Reports”, 1974 (Box 474, Folder 7)
    - East Texas Freedom Forum, 1970 (Box 474, Folder 8)
    - “Economic Council Letter”, 1959, 1960, 1963, 1964 (Box 474, Folder 9)
    - Education, 1962, 1974 (Box 474, Folder 10)
    - “Evolve”, Newton Armstrong Jr., 1962 (Box 474, Folder 11)
    - “Federal Spending Facts”, 1953 (Box 474, Folder 12)
    - Foundation for Economic Education, Inc., 1962 (Box 474, Folder 13)
    - Free Enterprise, 1962, 1964, 1970 (Box 474, Folder 14)
    - Freedom, 1952, 1961 (Box 474, Folder 15)
    - “Freedom in Action”, 1961 (Box 474, Folder 16)
    - Gun Control, 1970, 1974 (Box 474, Folder 17)
    - “The Gospel Truth”, 1974 (Box 474, Folder 18)
    - “Human Events”, 1959, 1962-1966 (Box 474, Folder 19)
    - Humanity Benefactor Foundation, undated (Box 474, Folder 20)
    - “Hunt for Truth”, H. L. Hunt, 1965 (Box 474, Folder 21)
    - Independence Foundation, 1968 (Box 474, Folder 22)
    - International Conspiracy, undated (Box 474, Folder 23)
    - “The John Birch Society is a Threat. To Whom?”, 1961 (Box 474, Folder 24)
    - Labor Unions, Right to Work, 1947-1955 (Box 474, Folder 25)
    - “Liberty Letter”, 1974 (Box 474, Folder 26)
    - Liberty Lobby, 1961-1963, 1970-1972 (Box 474, Folder 27)
    - “Liberty Lowdown”, 1974 (Box 474, Folder 28)
    - “Life Line”, 1961-1969 (Box 475, Folder 1)
    - Liquor, 1953, 1962 (Box 475, Folder 2)
    - March of Freedom, Presidential Edition, 1953 (Box 475, Folder 3)
    - “Manion Forum”, 1962-1963 (Box 475, Folder 4)
    - “National Message”, 1974 (Box 475, Folder 5)
    - “National Review”, 1974 (Box 475, Folder 6)
    - New Christian Crusade Church, undated (Box 475, Folder 7)
    - “The Nitty Gritty Truth”, 1974 (Box 475, Folder 8)
    - Patriotism, Max Rafferty Speeches, “Our Country”, 1952, 1961, 1963 (Box 475, Folder 9)
    - Racism, 1957-1972 (Box 475, Folder 10)
    - Religion, 1957-1970 (Box 475, Folder 11)
    - “Right or Wrong”, John E. Coogan, 1961-1962 (Box 475, Folder 12)
    - Riots, undated (Box 475, Folder 13)
    - “Second Declaration of Independence & Notice to Tyrants”, 1973 (Box 475, Folder 14)
    - Socialism, 1950s-60s (Box 475, Folder 15)
    - “Southern Conservative”, 1954 (Box 475, Folder 16)
    - “Southern Libertarian Messenger”, 1974 (Box 475, Folder 17)
    - Southern States Industrial Council, 1950s, 1960s (Box 475, Folder 18)
    - Texas Committee for the Constitution, Inc., 1974 (Box 475, Folder 19)
    - United Society of Methodist Laymen, 1955-1963 (Box 475, Folder 20)
    - Voice of Truth, 1967 (Box 475, Folder 21)
    - Washington Associated Committees for Better Government, Blaine W. Hodgen, 1965 (Box 476, Folder 1)
    - Washington Observer Newsletter, 1974 (Box 476, Folder 2)
    - White Majority, 1969 (Box 476, Folder 3)
    - Young Americans for Freedom, 1962 (Box 476, Folder 4)
  - Speeches, 1942-1986, undated; 8
    - Drafts, Handwritten (1 of 2), undated (Box 476, Folder 5)
    - Drafts, Handwritten (2 of 2), undated (Box 476, Folder 6)
    - Drafts, Handwritten, District Attorney Campaign, 1946 (Box 476, Folder 7)
    - Drafts, Message from East Texas by Merlin P. Davidson, Chairman, Friends for John Dowdy Election Committee, 1964 (Box 476, Folder 8)
    - Drafts, Odd Fellows, undated (Box 476, Folder 9)
    - Bible Study, God’s Covenant with Mankind, 1942 September 26 (Box 476, Folder 10)
    - God and Politics, 1943 August 15 (Box 476, Folder 11)
    - Brownsboro, 1944 April 30 (Box 476, Folder 12)
    - Eustace High School Commencement, 1944 May 22 (Box 476, Folder 13)
    - Odd Fellows Anniversary, 1944 June (Box 476, Folder 14)
    - Campaign for District Attorney (D.A.), 1945 (Box 476, Folder 15)
    - Rotary Club, 1945 January 11 (Box 476, Folder 16)
    - Presbyterian Church, Athens, 1945 November 18 (Box 476, Folder 17)
    - Ninth and Tenth Amendments, 1946 (Box 476, Folder 18)
    - Second Term District Attorney, 1946 (Box 476, Folder 19)
    - Lion’s Club, Ladies Night, Handwritten Notes, 1947 December 16 (Box 476, Folder 20)
    - District Attorney Campaign (1 of 3), 1948 (Box 476, Folder 21)
    - District Attorney Campaign (2 of 3), 1948 (Box 476, Folder 22)
    - District Attorney Campaign (3 of 3), 1948 (Box 476, Folder 23)
    - Henderson County, District Attorney Campaign, 1948 (Box 476, Folder 24)
    - San Pedro Memorial, 1948 (Box 476, Folder 25)
    - District Attorney Radio KNET, 1948 July 8 (Box 476, Folder 26)
    - Christmas Trades Day, 1949 (Box 476, Folder 27)
    - March of Dimes KBUD, 1950 February 2 (Box 476, Folder 28)
    - Old Fiddler’s Day Memorial, 1951 (Box 476, Folder 29)
    - No Title, Pre-1952 (Box 476, Folder 30)
    - Civic Club Speech, Pre-1952 (Box 476, Folder 31)
    - Corrigan, Pre-1952 (Box 476, Folder 32)
    - The Necessity of Law Enforcement, Pre-1952 (Box 476, Folder 33)
    - Campaign Speeches, 1952 (Box 476, Folder 34)
    - Faith in Our Schools and Communities, Nacogdoches, 1952 November 10 (Box 476, Folder 35)
    - Remarks, In the House, 1953 (Box 476, Folder 36)
    - Stewardship of Evangelism, 1953 (Box 476, Folder 37)
    - Value of a Library to an Individual, 1953 (Box 476, Folder 38)
    - What is Going to Happen to Post Offices Under the New Regime?, 1953-1954 (Box 476, Folder 39)
    - National Association of Postmasters and the National League of District Postmasters, 1953-1954 (Box 476, Folder 40)
    - What Your Congressman Can Do for You?, 1953-1954 (Box 477, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, 1953 February 3 (Box 477, Folder 2)
    - In Support of H.R. 4654, 1953 April 30 (Box 477, Folder 3)
    - Annual Odd Fellows Pilgrimage to the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, 1953 September 29 (Box 477, Folder 4)
    - Garrison High School Commencement, 1954 May 21 (Box 477, Folder 5)
    - Young Democrats of Washington, 1954 June 17 (Box 477, Folder 6)
    - Remarks, 1954 August 17 (Box 477, Folder 7)
    - National Federation of Federal Employees National Convention, Dallas, TX, Welcoming Remarks, 1954 September 13 (Box 477, Folder 8)
    - Declaration of Constitutional Principles, Segregation, Signed by Dowdy and Others, 1955 (Box 477, Folder 9)
    - Odd Fellows, 1955 (Box 477, Folder 10)
    - Postmasters, 7th District, 1955 (Box 477, Folder 11)
    - Remarks, In the House, 1955 (Box 477, Folder 12)
    - The Supreme Court, 1955 (Box 477, Folder 13)
    - National Association of Letter Carriers, 1955 September 10 (Box 477, Folder 14)
    - 52nd Annual Convention, National League of Postmasters, 1955 September 22 (Box 477, Folder 15)
    - Texas Federation of Retired Civil Service Employees, Tyler, TX, 1955 October 8 (Box 477, Folder 16)
    - Cotton, 1956 (Box 477, Folder 17)
    - Mailing of Unsolicited Materials, Gambling, Devices, and Obscene Materials, 1956 (Box 477, Folder 18)
    - Remarks, 1956 (Box 477, Folder 19)
    - National Federation of Federal Employees, 1956 June 2 (Box 477, Folder 20)
    - National Federation of Post Office Clerks, Houston, TX, 1956 June 22 (Box 477, Folder 21)
    - Fourth of July, 1956 July 4 (Box 477, Folder 22)
    - Palestine Farm Bureau, 1956 September 6 (Box 477, Folder 23)
    - DAR, Palestine, 1956 September 12 (Box 477, Folder 24)
    - Boiling Pot in the Middle East for Athens Christian Church Brotherhood, 1956 October 17 (Box 477, Folder 25)
    - Athens High School, 1956 November 28 (Box 477, Folder 26)
    - Eisenhower Program, 1957 (Box 477, Folder 27)
    - Post Office Budget, 1957 (Box 477, Folder 28)
    - Remarks, In the House, 1957 (Box 477, Folder 29)
    - Sputnik, 1957 (Box 477, Folder 30)
    - American Citizenship Month, 1957-1958 (Box 477, Folder 31)
    - Excerpts from Debate on H.R. 6127, Civil Rights, 1957 July 7 (Box 477, Folder 32)
    - IRS Regulations Under Federal Firearms Act, 1957 August 28 (Box 477, Folder 33)
    - Civic Club Speech, 1957 October 1 (Box 477, Folder 34)
    - Civic Club Speech, 1957 October 8 (Box 477, Folder 35)
    - Civic Club Speech, 1957 October 10 (Box 478, Folder 1)
    - Federal Aid/Education, 1957 November 11 (Box 478, Folder 2)
    - Christianity in Government and Politics, 1958 (Box 478, Folder 3)
    - Faith in Our Schools and Communities, 1958 (Box 478, Folder 4)
    - Remarks, U.S. House, 1958 (Box 478, Folder 5)
    - Obscene Material in the Mail, 1958 January 27 (Box 478, Folder 6)
    - Providence, RI, Commission on Youth, 1958 May 16 (Box 478, Folder 7)
    - 100F, Governor Frank G. Clement, 1958 September 25 (Box 478, Folder 8)
    - Remarks, U.S. House, 1959 (Box 478, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Dollar, Nacogdoches, TX, 1959 (Box 478, Folder 10)
    - Pornography and Obscenity, 1959 May 6 (Box 478, Folder 11)
    - Statement, House Post Office and Civil Service Subcommittee on Postal Operations, 1959 May 18 (Box 478, Folder 12)
    - Freedom is Won by Service, 1959 May 26 (Box 478, Folder 13)
    - Optimist Club, Pornography, 1959 June 3 (Box 478, Folder 14)
    - Mutual Security Act of 1954 Amendment, 1959 June 17 (Box 478, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 3, Congressional Record, 1959 June 23 (Box 478, Folder 16)
    - Rotary Club, Lufkin, TX, 1959 September 21 (Box 478, Folder 17)
    - Federal Employees, Crockett, TX, 1959 November (Box 478, Folder 18)
    - Connally Amendment, 1960 (Box 478, Folder 19)
    - Drift Toward Centralized Government, 1960 (Box 478, Folder 20)
    - Father-Son Banquet, Methodist Church, Vienna, VA, 1960 (Box 478, Folder 21)
    - Jacksonville, Kiwanis, 1960 (Box 478, Folder 22)
    - Postal Progress, 1960 (Box 478, Folder 23)
    - Remarks, U.S. House, 1960 (Box 478, Folder 24)
    - School Funding, 1960 (Box 478, Folder 25)
    - Taxes, Congressional Record, 1960 March 7 (Box 478, Folder 26)
    - Civil Rights, Congressional Record, 1960 March 11 (Box 478, Folder 27)
    - Preserve the National Forests, 1960 March 18 (Box 478, Folder 28)
    - Misnamed “Civil Rights” Bill a Tool of Tyranny, Congressional Record, 1960 March 21 (Box 478, Folder 29)
    - Rotary Club, Communism, Cuba, Castro, Sugar, 1960 July 22 (Box 478, Folder 30)
    - Mary Ellen College, 1960 September 28 (Box 478, Folder 31)
    - Basic Fundamentals of Government, 1960 October 27 (Box 478, Folder 32)
    - Legislative Contacts, 1960 October 27 (Box 478, Folder 33)
    - Extension of Remarks, 1961 (Box 478, Folder 34)
    - Remarks, In the House, 1961 (Box 478, Folder 35)
    - Texas Farm Bureau, San Antonio, TX, 1961 (Box 478, Folder 36)
    - The People of District, 1961 (Box 478, Folder 37)
    - Testimonial Dinner Response, Hotel Fredonia, Nacogdoches, TX, 1961 January 7 (Box 478, Folder 38)
    - T.V. Script, 1961 January 13 (Box 478, Folder 39)
    - Radio Speech, 1961 January 25 (Box 478, Folder 40)
    - Radio Speech, 1961 March 1 (Box 478, Folder 41)
    - Effects of Fellowship and Friendship Around the World for Rotary International, 1961 March 7 (Box 478, Folder 42)
    - Obscenity: Pornography and Delinquency, 1961 August 25 (Box 478, Folder 43)
    - 41st Anniversary Observance, 19th Amendment, 1961 August 28 (Box 478, Folder 44)
    - Importance of Ladies Participation in Modern Politics, Twentieth Century Reading Club, 1961 September 20 (Box 478, Folder 45)
    - 4-H Club, Palestine, 1961 November 11 (Box 478, Folder 46)
    - StatementELto U.S. Army EngineersELTrinity River Basin, 1961 December 20 (Box 478, Folder 47)
    - Compromise and Courage, Adapted from a Radio Speech, Jacksonville Employee-Employer Banquet, Lufkin Civic Club, 1962 (Box 478, Folder 48)
    - Foreign Aid, 1962 (Box 478, Folder 49)
    - History Repeats Itself or This is Where I Came In, Communism, 1962 (Box 479, Folder 1)
    - Postmasters, 2nd District, 1962 (Box 479, Folder 2)
    - Remarks, 1962 January 18 (Box 479, Folder 3)
    - Remarks, U.S. House, 1962 (Box 479, Folder 4)
    - The Record I Have Made, I Stand on It, 1962 March 21 (Box 479, Folder 5)
    - Radio Speech, 1961 May 30 (Box 479, Folder 6)
    - Building on Our Heritage, 4-H Clubs, Trinidad, 1962 June 19 (Box 479, Folder 7)
    - Post Office Dedication, Palestine, TX, 1962 September 14 (Box 479, Folder 8)
    - Radio Speech, Handwritten, 1962 September 17 (Box 479, Folder 9)
    - Radio Speech, Handwritten, 1962 September 18 (Box 479, Folder 10)
    - Cuba Revolution, 1962 September 26 (Box 479, Folder 11)
    - Radio Speech, Handwritten, 1962 October 2 (Box 479, Folder 12)
    - Sparkler Manufacturing Company, President’s “E” Award, 1962 October 30 (Box 479, Folder 13)
    - Extension of Remarks, 1963 (Box 479, Folder 14)
    - Urban Renewal, 1963 (Box 479, Folder 15)
    - Rural Areas Development Program, 1963 January 15 (Box 479, Folder 16)
    - Livestock Industry’s Stake in the Wheat Referendum, 1963 April 11 (Box 479, Folder 17)
    - Police and Fireman’s Memorial Service, 1963 May 19 (Box 479, Folder 18)
    - Postal Facility Dedication, Lufkin, 1963 May 25 (Box 479, Folder 19)
    - Old Fiddler’s Contest, Athens, TX, 1963 May 31 (Box 479, Folder 20)
    - Liberty Lobby School of Politics, 1963 August 26 (Box 479, Folder 21)
    - Birmingham, AL, 1963 September 19 (Box 479, Folder 22)
    - Birmingham, AL, 1963 November (Box 479, Folder 23)
    - Urban Renewal, Restaurant Beverage Association, 1963 November (Box 479, Folder 24)
    - Appreciation Dinner, Lufkin, 1963 (Box 479, Folder 25)
    - In the House, Refers to the Kennedy Assassination, 1963 December 5 (Box 479, Folder 26)
    - Freedom Forum, Athens, TX, 1963 December (Box 479, Folder 27)
    - Americanism vs. Communism, Freedom Forum and American Legion, 1963 December 30 (Box 479, Folder 28)
    - Cherokee County, 1964 (Box 479, Folder 29)
    - Mob Violence, 1964 (Box 479, Folder 30)
    - Palestine High School, 1964 (Box 479, Folder 31)
    - Privilege of American Citizenship, 1964 (Box 479, Folder 32)
    - Reelection Speech, 1964 (Box 479, Folder 33)
    - Remarks, U.S. House, 1964 (Box 480, Folder 1)
    - Water Conservation, 1964 (Box 480, Folder 2)
    - Jacksonville Kiwanis, 1964 January 2 (Box 480, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights, A Totalitarian Proposal, 1964 February 1 (Box 480, Folder 4)
    - Urban Renewal Problems, Dayton Lawyers Club, Dayton, Ohio, 1964 February 8 (Box 480, Folder 5)
    - D.A.R., Lufkin, TX, 1964 February 18 (Box 480, Folder 6)
    - Tribute to Congressman Frank Horton, 1964 February 20 (Box 480, Folder 7)
    - Washington Rebekahs, 1965 March (Box 480, Folder 8)
    - The Mounting Scandal of Urban Renewal, 1964 March 4 (Box 480, Folder 9)
    - Columbia Plaza Project, National Conference on Urban Renewal, Rackford, Ill., 1964 March 12 (Box 480, Folder 10)
    - Allen Chapel Methodist Church, Athens, TX, 1964 March 9 (Box 480, Folder 11)
    - Political Rally, Athens and Other Political Rallies, 1964 March 10 (Box 480, Folder 12)
    - This is My Record, 1964 March 17 (Box 480, Folder 13)
    - Dowdy Report, 1964 March 19 (Box 480, Folder 14)
    - Reelection Speech for T.V., 1964 April 2 (Box 480, Folder 15)
    - Urban Renewal, 1964 April 4 (Box 480, Folder 16)
    - Reelection Speech for T.V., 1964 May 1 (Box 480, Folder 17)
    - St. Paul Industrial Training School, Henderson County, TX, 1964 May 31 (Box 480, Folder 18)
    - Goals, Graduation Speech, 1964 (Box 480, Folder 19)
    - Urban Renewal, 1964 June 22 (Box 480, Folder 20)
    - Attack by William L. Slayton, 1964 June 25 (Box 480, Folder 21)
    - Maladministration of Federal Urban Renewal, 1964 June 25 (Box 480, Folder 22)
    - Urban Renewal, 1964 July 12 (Box 480, Folder 23)
    - Radio Speech, Handwritten, 1964 July 17 (Box 480, Folder 24)
    - Campaign Speech, 1964 October (Box 480, Folder 25)
    - Radio Address, 1964 October 6 (Box 480, Folder 26)
    - Tyler Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1964 October 28 (Box 480, Folder 27)
    - Nacogdoches Optimist Club, 1964 November 10 (Box 480, Folder 28)